Payam Zahedi



Contact

WebSite:

payamzahedi.com

Phone:

+98 9216516648

Email:

pzahedi1995@gmail.com

Social Links

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>Telegram</u> twitter

Dev Links

GitHub Stack OverFlow Medium

Languages

Persian – Native speaker English – Very good command

Hobbies

Learning, Basketball, Music and Dota 2

Summary

I'm a Software Engineer that fluent in Java, dart, Python, Kotlin languages and Flutter, Android, Django Frameworks. With more than 6 years of programming experience. Familiarity with Fire Base Services, Analytics Services, Google Map API ... with team spirit. I love learning and I love my Happiness.

Skill Highlights

- Android Development
- Android studio
- Java, Kotlin
- OOP
- Git
- Agile and Scrum
- MVVM, MVP
- RxJava, RxAndroid
- Cryptography

- Flutter Development
- Dart
- Python, Django
- BLoC
- Dio
- Material Design
- Unit Testing
- Restful Api
- Web socket

Experience

Mobile Developer - at RaSecret mobile app Jun, 2019 to Sep, 2020 – Remote

Mobile Developer - at Dropp Technologies Group Jun, 2019 to Sep, 2019 – Gorgan

Developer - at **Self-employed** Dec, 2018 to May, 2019 - Gorgan

Android Developer - at Targeting Company Jan, 2016 to Sep, 2019 - Gorgan

Education

Master's degree: Islamic Azad University of Gorgan - 2019 Bachelor: Islamic Azad University of Gorgan - 2017

Associately degrees. Chahid Champun Huivensity of Causen

Associate's degree: Shahid Chamran University of Gorgan - 2014

Courses

Udacity Android: **Developing Android Apps with Kotlin.**Udacity Flutter: **Build Native Mobile Apps with Flutter.**